//creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"In what year was laliga formed?",
        answer: "1929",
        options:[
            "1992",
            "1956",
            "1929",
            "1966"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"which is the only club outside FC Barcelona and Real madrid who had never played outside spainish top division football ",
        answer: "Athletic Club",
        options:[
            "Real Sociedad",
            "Villarreal",
            "Atletico Madrid",
            "Athletic Club"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Who is the only African footballer to win the La Liga Golden Boot?",
        answer: "Samuel Eto'o",
        options:[
            "Samuel Eto'o",
            "Salif Keita",
            "Seydou Keita",
            "Rabah Madjer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"Who managed FC Barcelona to their only title of the 1980s, in 1984-85?",
        answer: "Terry Venables",
        options:[
            "Johan Cruyff",
            "Frank Rijkaard",
            "Jose Mari Bakero",
            "Terry Venables"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Who has made the most La Liga apperances?",
        answer: "Andoni Zubizarreta",
        options:[
            "Sergio Aguero",
            "lionel Messi",
            "Andoni Zubizarreta",
            "Carlos puyol"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"Who is the all time goal scorer of La Liga?(474)",
        answer: "Lionel Messi",
        options:[
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Raul",
            "Alfredo Di Stefano",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"Which goal keeper has the most clean sheets in the La Liga History?",
        answer: "Andoni Zubizarreta",
        options:[
            "Iker Casillas",
            "Andoni Zubizarreta",
            "Luis Arconada",
            "Paco Buyo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Which manger has won most La Liga title as Manager?",
        answer: "Miguel Munoz",
        options:[
            "Miguel Munoz",
            "Helenio Herrera",
            "Johan Cruyff",
            "Enrique Fernandez"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"Which company is the current main sponsor of La Liga?",
        answer: "Santander",
        options:[
            "Adidas",
            "Nike",
            "Puma",
            "Santander"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"Which La Liga team had won the most Champions League?(13 titles)",
        answer: "Real Madrid",
        options:[
            "Barcelona",
            "Atletico Madrid",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Valencia"
        ]
    },
];